### Mykola Avramuk

#### Personal information

Date of birth: 16.12.1995

Home: Kyiv

Location: Barcelona

Email: <a href="mailto:avramuk89@gmail.com">avramuk89@gmail.com</a>
LinkedIn: <a href="mailto:linkedin.com/in/avramukk">linkedin.com/in/avramukk</a>
Github: <a href="mailto:github.com/avramukk">github.com/avramukk</a>

Website: avramukk.com

# **Summary of Qualifications**

3 years of IT experience in development

5 years of experience in the IT Engineering on the TV

## **Expertise**

Test planning and strategy development

Functional and non-functional testing

Regression testing, API manual, and automation testing

Project management and delivery

Bash, Python, JS/TS

Playwright, Cypress, Postman

AWS(EC2, ECS, S3, Lambda), Github Actions, Gitlab CI

REST API, Docker, Grafana, Git

Linux, Windows, macOS, Android, iOS

SDI and IP video transport, Oasys System, and vMix

MPEG (2,4,HEVC) Video, SRT, Zixi, RTMP, HLS, WebRTC, NDI, FFMPEG, Gstreamer

#### Languages

English - intermediate Ukrainian – native

### **Experience**

**QA** Engineer

Switcher.ai, Contract Mar 2022 – Present

Responsibility: Full QA process of SDLC for the cloud video switcher Technology: Live Video Streaming, Linux, Web, SRT, RTMP, Zixi

QA Engineer & Project Manager

**VVCR**, Contract

Jul 2020 – Present

Responsibility: Full QA process from scratch of cloud-based virtual video control room system

(VVCR). Managing SDLC in the team of 4 people

Technology: Scrum, Test Planning, System Testing, Regression Testing, Live Video Streaming, API

Testing, Manual Testing, Test Automation

**QA** Engineer

**RIVET**, Contract

Jul 2020 - Present

Responsibility:

Full QA process from scratch of Broadcast Tools (Windows, macOS, iOS, Android) and Platform (web) for Remote Streaming via SRT Protocols.

Technology: Test Planning, System Testing, Regression Testing, Live Video Streaming, API Testing, Manual Testing, Test Automation

Video Streaming Engineer <u>1+1 MEDIA</u>, Shift-time Aug 2018 - Jul 2020

Responsibility: Live video streaming, Installation and support of devices and applications for

broadcasts

Technology: AWS Elemental Live, LiveU Central, vMix, OBS, FFmpeg, RTMP, HLS, UDP

**Broadcasting Automation Engineer** 

112 TV channel, Shift-time

Mar 2020 - Jun 2021

Responsibility: Servers Administering for Video Content Delivery pipeline for post production

Technology: Windows Server, Linux, MacOS, Avid Technology Products

IT Support Engineer 112 TV channel, Shift-time Feb 2018 - May 2020

Responsibility: Technical Support

Technology: Windows, MacOS, Linux, Avid Technology Products

Broadcast Specialist

112 TV channel, Shift-time

Sep 2016 - Feb 2018

Responsibility: Broadcast quality control, planning of the broadcast grid, quick response to any

problems in the final broadcast signal

Technology: Oasys Air System, Broadcasting, Television

### **Educational background**

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" Master's degree, Intellectual technologies of microsystem radio-electronic equipment Sep 2017 - Sep 2018

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" Bachelor's degree, Telecommunications and radio engineering Sep 2013 - Aug 2017